http://www.allensponyexpress.com/privacy-notice

HomeShopPrivacy NoticeHow To MeasureAbout UsMoreHomeShopPrivacy NoticeHow To MeasureAbout UsHomeShopPrivacy NoticeHow To MeasureAbout Us
Your Privacy Matters Privacy Notice  This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for www.AllensPonyExpress.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:
1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
4. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
5. How policy changes will be communicated.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will NOT sell or rent this information to anyone.  We hate spam more than you do!
Information We Collect
When you place an order you will need to give us your name, shipping and billing address. You can give us your email and phone if you choose. It will help us to get in touch with you if there are questions or problems with your order.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
We may also call you regarding an order if there is a problem, if we need to clarify something about the order or to let you know it will ship late.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website: · See what data we have about you, if any. · Change/correct any data we have about you. · Have us delete any data we have about you. · Express any concern you have about our use of your data. Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
All credit card information is deleted first by shredder, then by burning the shredded paper. We do not keep credit card information on file, you will have to give it every time you place an order. We are sorry for any inconvenience this may cause for you, but feel it is the most secure way to handle it.
Changes to this Policy
We may make changes to this privacy notice from time to time.  You may check back on this page at any time to see our current policy.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 618-273-3101 or via email at AllensPonyExpress@gmail.com
Copyright © 2018 Allen's Pony Express - All Rights Reserved.Privacy NoticeHow To Measure
